<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>James Lloyd</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on James Lloyd</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code Name Long Neck</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-17-code-name-long-neck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-17-code-name-long-neck/</guid>
      <description>In a world of shadows and secrets, a seasoned spy uncovers a sinister plot to assassinate the President. But as he races to expose the truth, he finds himself hunted not only by enemy agents but also by an enigmatic force: ninja giraffes.&#xA;Synopsis: Alex Mason, a veteran intelligence operative, stumbles upon fragmented whispers of a high-level conspiracy. His instincts tell him it&amp;rsquo;s tied to the upcoming G20 Summit, where the President is a prime target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Giraffes Ate My Crewmate</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-space-giraffes-ate-my-crewmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-space-giraffes-ate-my-crewmate/</guid>
      <description>Short Pitch: When a routine mission to the International Space Station turns deadly, astronaut Commander Alex Mason returns to Earth with a bizarre tale of extraterrestrial murder. Haunted by the gruesome death of his partner and the horrifying sight of the Space Giraffes responsible, Mason embarks on a desperate quest to warn the world of the leafy green-loving menace lurking beyond the stars. But as his sanity unravels and the evidence mounts against him, Mason must confront a chilling truth: the real danger might not be in outer space, but within himself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2StateReviews.com</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/2statereviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/2statereviews/</guid>
      <description>I have built 2statereviews.com with Darren Watt. The site is based on Darrens long time Film reccomendation system which has only 2 states See! or Dont See!. Simplicity at its best, the site allows you to search for films and vote See, Dont See for them, warning though its quite addictive. The site is currently 80% feature complete ( this figure changes constantly as we make up new features).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Enterprise Desktop in a Digital Age</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-an-enterprise-desktop-in-a-digital-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-an-enterprise-desktop-in-a-digital-age/</guid>
      <description>A path to creating a people centric desktop.&#xA;Currently in an Enterprise The enterprise desktop is a complex beast. Provisioning and maintaining 1000+ clients is not a simple task. Ensuring your estate is configured to work with your network and complies with your company’s security policies requires layer upon layer of management.&#xA;Full OS refreshes requires multi-million $ programme that span multiple years and geographies, creating large capital spikes. As these large cumbersome programmes finish their impressive task, you’ll find due to the ever increasing pace of change that the once new and shiny OS you just deployed to your enterprise is now out of date, about to go end of life and you need to get back on the merry-go-round and start again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duplicati Discord Notifications</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/duplicati-discord-notifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/duplicati-discord-notifications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHP Active Directory Search</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/php-active-directory-search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/php-active-directory-search/</guid>
      <description>Just add the fully qualified domain name of your domain controller (host), the domain dn ( if your domain was beanz.meanz.heinz.com for example your dn would be DC=beanz,DC=meanz,DC=heinz,DC=com ) supply the username and password of a user in your domain, this user does not need to be a member of any group, as long as the account isn’t disabled. Then your off!You can add active directory attributes to the $search_fields array to change what you can search on You can add which active directory attributes are displayed in the result by adding to the $return_fields array</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
