<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movie Pitch on James Lloyd</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/movie-pitch/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movie Pitch on James Lloyd</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/movie-pitch/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code Name Long Neck</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-17-code-name-long-neck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 16:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-17-code-name-long-neck/</guid>
      <description>In a world of shadows and secrets, a seasoned spy uncovers a sinister plot to assassinate the President. But as he races to expose the truth, he finds himself hunted not only by enemy agents but also by an enigmatic force: ninja giraffes.&#xA;Synopsis: Alex Mason, a veteran intelligence operative, stumbles upon fragmented whispers of a high-level conspiracy. His instincts tell him it&amp;rsquo;s tied to the upcoming G20 Summit, where the President is a prime target.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space Giraffes Ate My Crewmate</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-space-giraffes-ate-my-crewmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024-08-16-space-giraffes-ate-my-crewmate/</guid>
      <description>Short Pitch: When a routine mission to the International Space Station turns deadly, astronaut Commander Alex Mason returns to Earth with a bizarre tale of extraterrestrial murder. Haunted by the gruesome death of his partner and the horrifying sight of the Space Giraffes responsible, Mason embarks on a desperate quest to warn the world of the leafy green-loving menace lurking beyond the stars. But as his sanity unravels and the evidence mounts against him, Mason must confront a chilling truth: the real danger might not be in outer space, but within himself.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
